Guide to The Leo Deaner Radical Left-Wing Publications collection, 1890-2017 LAC0011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- By Topic, Series 6
  - Women's Movement, 1970 - 1990; Series 6 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    Titles include: Alliance Against Women's Oppression, Women and the Cuban Revolution, Fighting for Women's Rights in the 1990s, Women's Studies in Italy, Amnlae: Born in the Struggle
  - Women's Movement, 1972 - 1983; Series 6 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    Titles include: Take Back Your Life: A Wimmin's guide to Alternative Health Care
  - Women's Movement, 1972 - 2010; Series 6 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    Titles include: Broken Bodies/Shattered Minds, Crimes of Hate/Conspiracy of Silence, Sex/Family and the New Right
  - Women's Movement, 1972 - 2017; Series 6 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    Titles include: Women of Vietnam, Anarchism: The Feminist Connection, Black Women Organising, Population and Imperialism Women in Revolution, Women and Class
  - Women's Movement, 1973 - 1976; Series 6 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    Titles include: Radical Women Manifesto-Theory Program and Struggle
  - Women's Movement, 1973 - 1982; Series 6 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Women's Movement, 1973 - 1993; Series 6 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Women's Movement, 1973 - 2002; Series 6 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    Titles include: Comrades and Sister: Women and the Struggle for Liberation, Women in Health, the Poverty of Feminism, Anarcho Feminism from Siren and Black Rose, Black Military Women of WWII
  - Women's Movement, 1973 - 2003; Series 6 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    Titles include: A Divorce Trial in China, Helen Keller, Women and the New World, Since When Has Working Been a Crime? The Deportation of Mexicans Without Papers, Mink Coats Don't Trickle Down- The economic attack on women and people of color, A Beginning Analysis of the Woman Question, Women Under Torture
  - Worker's League / Socialist Equality Party, 1990 - 2018; Series 6 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    Titles include: The War Comes Home- Race Clsss and Political Violence in America, The Political Significance of the U.S. Oil Workers' Strike, Flint: A Crime of Capitalism, The Lessons of Wisconsin, Socialism and the Defense of Public Education, the Great Autoworkers' Struggle of 2015, Los Angeles: The Class Issues, The Trial of Juan Farinas, Death on the Picket Line- the Story of John McCoy
  - Working Women, 1973 - 2012; Series 6 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    Titles include: Women Organizing the Office, Women Living the Strike, Women in the Labor Movement- California state federation of labor women's conference, Radical Women in the House of Labor: An Historic Re-Entry, Opium Women
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1918 - 2011; Series 6 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    Titles include: the Transitional Programme
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1928 - 2002; Series 6 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1931 - 1980; Series 6 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    Titles include: In Defense of the Soviet Union, Stalin's Frame-Up System and the Moscow trials, Leon Trotsky on Black Nationalism and Self Determination, the Red Book: Trotsky's Son Exposes the Moscow trials
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1947 - 2017; Series 6 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    Titles include: Marxism in the United States, Their Morals and Ours- Marxist Versus Liberal Views of Morality
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1948 - 1980; Series 6 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    Titles include: The 153 year Struggle for the American Labor Party
  - Works by Leon Trotsky, 1973 - 2015; Series 6 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    Titles include: Stalin's Gangsters, the General Strike, Women and the Family
  - Civil Rights, 1963 - 2018; Series 6 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Ireland, circa 1970 - 1983; Series 6 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    Titles include: Angela D'arcy, Violations of Human Rights in Northern Ireland 1968-1978, The British Media and Ireland
    Tone, Theobald Wolfe, 1763-1798, Tone, Wolfe, 1763-1798
  - Labor Movement, 1939 - 1995; Series 6 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    Titles include: Baltimore Joint Board, the Blacks and the Unions
  - Marxism - Leninism / NCM, 1970 - 1978; Series 6 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - New Left, 1972- 2008; Series 6 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    Titles include: For the People's Eyes Only: Papers on the War and Watergate, Mailing List of Movement Organizations, Corporate Crime Comics, Ronald Reagan: The Frontier Restored?, Red Diaper Baby playbill, Greatest Morons in History: Dan Quayle, Steal Back Your Vote
  - New Left - The State of Michigan v. John Sinclair, circa 1968; Series 6 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - SDS / ERAP, 1964 - 1970; Series 6; Hayden, Tom (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Socialism - Bulletin No.1-3, 1969 - 1970; Series 6 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Socialism / Socialist Labor Party (SLP), 1935 - 1975; Series 6 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    Titles include: Two Pages from Roman History, Capitalism Means War, The Labor Draft-Step to Industrial Slavery, The Nazi Beast Wars, The Commune: Paris 1871, Socialist Committees of Correspondence New York and Philidelphia Bulletin 1970
  - Trotskyism, 1942 - 1992; Series 6 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Phillipines, 1975 - 1993; Series 6 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    Titles include: Pumipiglas- Political Detension and Military Atrocities in the Philippines, the Age of Discovery: Impact on Philippine culture and Society, The Filippina- A Humanizing Force in Philippine Development